跟着你的倒数
On your marks.
准备好
Get set.
大开杀戒
Kill.
死亡飞车 全球最火爆的比赛
Death Race, the number one sport in the world,
在终端岛举行
located on Terminal Island.
历时三天的严酷比赛 罪犯们
Convicts race over the course of three grueling days
为那个终极大奖而厮杀
for the chance at the ultimate prize.
赢得五场比赛
Win five races,
赢取他的自由
win your freedom.
抢先预定下一场死亡飞车
Preorder the next Death Race now
您将不仅得到八折优惠
and you'll not only get 20% off,
更将获得限量版Frankenstein纪念商品
but you'll also receive limited edition Frankenstein merchandise.
Frankenstein 四场死亡飞车比赛的冠军
Frankenstein, the four-time Death Race champion,
已风靡全球
has taken the world by storm.
这位名不经转车手
The most unlikely of heroes
不可思议的出现
who has come out of nowhere
再赢一场比赛 他就将重获自由
and is now just one win away from freedom.
死亡飞车
Death Race.
正在直播
Now streaming live.
死亡飞车是Weyland国际集团的注册商标
Death Race is the trademark of Weyland International.
您的安全是我们的首要目标
Your safety's our top priority.
臭名昭著的死亡飞车选手Frankenstein
The notorious Death Racer known only as Frankenstein
今天赢得了个人第四场胜利
won his fourth race today.
再赢一场 这位戴着面具的杀手将获得自己的自由
One more victory and the masked killer gains his freedom.
无所畏惧的Frankenstein
Frankenstein fears nothing.
挡其道者 尽诛之
Anything in his way, he destroys.
在我的经营下 终端岛和死亡飞车正不断发展
Under my watch, Terminal Island and Death Race have thrived.
有传言称 举办死亡飞车比赛的
Rumors have been going around that Weyland International,
Weyland国际集团
the organization behind Death Race,
将被恶意收购
has been targeted for hostile takeover.
对于商人来说 被收购早已习以为常
As a businessman, takeover talk is common.
手握值钱的东西 自然有人想要夺走它
You have something of value, naturally, people want to take it away.
英国亿万富翁 Niles York
British billionaire, Niles York,
已将自己置于风口浪尖
has placed himself in the center of a firestorm.
眼下的舆论我暂时不做评价
Well, I've got nothing to say about that at the moment.
但我说一句
But I will say this.
我想得到任何东西 没有一个人能阻止我
When I want something, no one can stop me from taking it.
我并不担心 我赢下的从来比输掉的多
I'm not too concerned. I've won more battles than I've lost.
我真替Weyland可惜 真的
I feel bad for Weyland, I really do.
但岁月不饶人啊 他已经不行了
But Father Time, he's caught up with the old man.
毫无还手之力
He never really stood a chance.
《死亡飞车3：地狱烈焰》
早上好 Weyland先生
Good morning, Mr. Weyland.
也没那么糟糕 是吧?
Wasn't so bad, was it?
这节目是我起的
I built this business.
我没必要来偷
I didn't have to steal it.
我抓住了你的弱点 我不是偷
What you left vulnerable, I seized. I stole nothing.
你没有眼界 Weyland 这是你的祸根
You lacked vision, Weyland. That was your undoing.
眼界
Vision.
这就是你给全世界各种荒废的监狱投资百万的原因吗?
Is that why you're investing millions in dilapidated prisons all around the globe?
眼界?
Vision?
你都昏了头 把自己埋进地下
You're so far over your head, you might as well be six feet under the ground.
监狱产业不是这个公司盈利的项目
The prison business is not what made this company profitable.
所以你的目的是
So the conclusion to draw,
你想把死亡飞车做成全球联锁的节目
you're trying to franchise Death Race.
没戏的
It's not going to work.
因为你没做成吧
Because you couldn't make it work.
给你看看我们未来的伟大宏图
Let me show you what true vision really looks like.
你起了个好头 Weyland
You started something beautiful, Weyland.
但你只做了皮毛
But you only scratched at the surface.
你说对了 我是想把死亡飞车推向全球
And you're right. I'm taking Death Race global.
一年之内 每两周就会有一场比赛
By this time next year, there will be a different race every two weeks
在一个地狱般的地方举行 不同的车手不同的赛道和挑战
at a different exotic hellhole with different drivers, tracks and challenges.
我会垄断这个星球上 有史以来最赚钱的体育运动
I will have a monopoly on the most profitable sport in the history of the planet.
更多车 更多罪犯 更多火拼
More cars. More cons. More guns.
更多的死亡 没有极限
More death. The sky's the limit.
但 你忘了一件事
Well, you forgot one thing.
还有Frankenstein
Frankenstein.
这是个戴面具的人
It's a man in a mask.
我能找20个Frankenstein出来
I could have 20 Frankensteins around the globe.
观众怎么知道哪个才是真的?
How would the fans know which one was real?
Frankenstein今天赢了第四场比赛
Frankenstein won his fourth race today.
再赢一场 他就自由了
One more win, he goes free.
这是每一个观众都知道的事实
That's a fact that every fan knows.
你现在要是突然改变比赛规则
Now, if you suddenly change the rules of the game,
你就留不住观众了
you're going to lose your audience.
要是你指望Frankenstein会输
And if you're hoping that Frankenstein loses,
好吧 我想他之前还没输过
well, son, I guess there's a first time.
如此一来 没有他 你这拷贝不走样的节目
Now, how would your little copycat event play
怎么继续下去?
without the game's marquee star?
这就是你注定失败的原因
That's why you're going to fail.
Weyland 你抽什么牌子的雪茄?
What kind of cigars you smoke, Weyland?
等死亡飞车享誉全球的时候 我一定会给你寄上一盒
I'll be sure to send you a box when Death Race becomes a global success.
我就会第二次打败你 也是你又一次输给我
It'll be the second time I've beaten you. The second time you've lost.
那 趁有机会的时候好好享受吧
Well, you enjoy your moment while you can.
这结局你不会喜欢的
Payback's a bitch, son.
Weyland没说错
Weyland's right.
给我查那个面具背后的人是谁
Find out who the man behind the mask really is.
他的所爱所憎 最觊觎什么
What he loves, what he hates, what he covets most.
还有Weyland下一步计划是什么
And find out what Weyland was planning next.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
他公司一周内为了做Frankenstein联锁产业
The company's banking nearly eight million quid a week
投了将近800万
hawking Frankenstein merchandise.
他不会轻易放手的
He wasn't just gonna let it go.
还有别的吗?
Anything else?
有 给自己买点像样的衣服 你看上去就像个捡破烂的
Yeah. Get yourself some decent clothes. You look like a bag lady.
如果我热爱死亡飞车 我都不会出现在这里 做这笔买卖
I wouldn't be here, I wouldn't have done all this unless I absolutely loved Death Race.
所以我要告诉全世界 数以万计死亡飞车的铁杆观众
So I'm speaking to the millions of fans around the globe.
不用担心 我和大家一样
Fear not. I am like you.
我不会破坏或者牺牲我们所恪守的一切
I seek not to destroy nor to compromise what we've all come to revere.
我们所知和所爱的死亡飞车不会改变
The Death Race that we all know and love will not change.
它会变得更壮大更完美 这 我向大家保证
It will grow bigger and better. This, I promise.
谢谢各位
Thank you.
总体来说我很满意
Overall, I have to say I'm very happy.
你想看看吗?
You wanna take a look?
不必了
No.
我们明天再做一些测试
We'll run a few more tests tomorrow,
然后你就能回到正常生活了
and you're back to your old self in no time.
其实不然
No, he won't.
他会变得更好
He'll be better.
所有人都出去
Everybody out.
都听到了吧 出去喝杯咖啡吧
You heard the man. Take a coffee break, guys.
看来 传言是真的
So, I guess the rumors are true.
是啊 你也不会为我惋惜吧
Yeah, and I guess you won't be shedding any tears for me.
Carl 你和我 这辈子走过的路完全不同
Hey, you and I, Carl, we've taken very different paths in life.
但却都走到了这一步
But we both ended up here.
不 是我坐在这里
No, I'm here.
而你是来去自如 可以见自己爱的人
You come and go as you please, see the ones you love.
他们也见得到你
They see you.
别拿我们做比较 Weyland 你丢了公司
Don't compare us, Weyland. You lost the company.
- 我丢了生活  - 没错
- I lost my life.  - Mmm-hmm.
我还修好了你的脸 给你一条出路
Yeah, and I also fixed your face and I gave you a way out.
看着我 告诉我你会信守诺言
Look at me and tell me you were gonna keep your word.
Weyland 我不傻
I'm not stupid, Weyland.
你不是出于良心才帮我整容的 是吧?
And you didn't fix my face out of the kindness of your heart, did you?
我伤口已经感染了 我就要死了
It was infected. I was gonna die.
你的明星车手就要没了
And you would have lost your star driver.
是啊你没这么坏 你只是更毒
Yeah, you're not so bad. You're worse.
你要我相信你?
And you want me to trust you?
你现在深陷泥潭就是活该
You deserve the shit-storm you're in.
我有新消息 Carl
Well, I got news for you, Carl.
你已经逃不掉了
You're already in waist-deep.
你是Frankenstein
You're Frankenstein.
一切由你开始 由你结束
This all starts and ends with you.
他叫Carl Lucas
Carl Lucas.
自幼便入黑帮
Born a gangster,
被囚于铁窗之后
became a prisoner,
现在 他已是一个禽兽
and now, a monster.
愿他安息
May he rest in peace.
你和你的团队赢五场比赛
You and your team win five races
你们就能获得自由
and you go free.
Goldberg 以及Lists
Goldberg, Lists
还有那个美丽动人的Katrina
and that beautiful, beautiful Katrina.
现在 为了你们成功
Now, for this to work,
你不能告诉别人你的真实身份
you can't tell your true identity to anyone.
Carl Lucas已经死了
Carl Lucas stays dead.
你是Frankenstein
You're Frankenstein.
不用客气 混蛋
Well, you're welcome, asshole.
赢了四场 一个谢谢都没有
Four wins and not even a thank you.
一切由你开始 由你结束
This all starts and ends with you.
他来了 就是他啊
There he is. There's the guy.
我帮你转狱了
I'm having you transferred.
你要去南非的Kalahari沙漠最高戒备监狱
You're headed to the Kalahari Desert Maximum Security Penitentiary
去完成第一场沙漠死亡飞车比赛
in South Africa where you will compete in the first ever Desert Death Race.
哦? 会给我配自己的沙漠越野车吗?
Wow. What do I get, my own dune buggy?
只不过是借你去Kalahari
You're just on loan to the Kalahari
帮着开各种死亡飞车国际赛的第一场
to help launch the first of what will be many international Death Races.
我们会带上14K 还有你的团队
We're sending 14K, as well as both your teams.
看来得更新我的护照了
So I'm guessing I should get my passport updated.
你貌似不把我当回事儿
I get the feeling that you are not taking me seriously.
因为我不把你当回事儿
That's because I'm not.
听着 我和Weyland说好了
Listen to me. I made a deal with Weyland.
我再赢一场 我 还有我的团队
I win one more race, me, my team,
都能出狱
we're out.
你也知道 Weyland的事挺可惜的
Yeah, well, you know, it's a pity about Weyland,
因为你和他做的交易都不作数了
because all deals with him are null and void.
现在你帮我办事 我的规矩
You work for me now. New rules.
做梦
No.
我想不是吧
No, I don't think so.
没人给你选吧 你要不想开
You don't have a choice, mate. But if you don't want to drive,
好啊
fine.
我用你的血 把我飞机喷成红色
I will paint my plane red with your blood.
真的吗?
Really?
就你?
Niles?
你怎么打算 找人替我?
What are you gonna do, replace me?
找谁呢?
With who?
你担心什么? 你已经死了
Why would you care? You're already dead.
所以 只要你活着 你就会有明星的待遇
So, as long as you're alive, you'll be treated like the star that you are.
或者
Or,
我轻而易举地打乱你的计划
I could just simply fuck up your little plan,
是吧 只要再赢一场
couldn't I, by winning one more race
我就自由了
and I'm free.
哈哈 你不会过终点的
Wow. You'll never make it to the finish line, mate.
相信我
Trust me on that.
输掉比赛 你活下去 赢了比赛 你见鬼去
You lose, you live. You win, you die.
(南非)
快 下车!
Okay, get out!
快点 走起来!
Let's go, move!
把那手提钻拿来
Bring that jackhammer here.
站好队伍! 快点!
Get in the line! Get moving!
大家快看呐!
Boy, take a look at those!
快点走
Move your fuckin' arse.
这是谁?
Who's that?
嘿 Goldberg!
Hey, Goldberg!
是你啊
Yeah, that's right.
我可是你们的铁杆车迷
I'm a big fan. But we've got our own bitches down here.
你还带自己的人来干嘛
I don't know why you brought yours along.
要不我给你签个名
Hey, let me give you an autograph.
快走! 快走!
Move! Move!
把这关节卸了怎么样!
Let's take this fucking joint!
杀了他们!
Kill them all!
- 快建立防线  - 马上趴到地上!
- Set up a perimeter now.  - On the ground, now!
该死!
Shit!
起来!
Get up!
你还好吗? 这是?
Are you hurt? What?
Lucas 一直都是你
Lucas. It always was you.
你这个混蛋!
You son of a bitch!
我们都以为你死了
We thought you were dead.
所以一直是你戴着面具在比赛
So it's always been you behind the mask.
没错 但说来话长
Yeah, it's a long story.
你和他们做了什么交易?
So what kind of deal did they make, huh?
我没有选择
I didn't have a choice.
看来不管是什么交易 他们都答应帮你整容
Whatever it was, it included getting your face fixed.
我看到了 我就在现场
I saw it. I was there.
是吗 Goldberg?
Did you, Goldberg?
还是你只看到了他们想让你看到的一面?
Or did you just see what they wanted you to see?
他们想让我们看到什么?
What did they want us to see?
根本就没有交易
That is no deal.
你根本不用做交易
You never needed to make a deal.
你只要连续赢五场比赛 你就自由了
All you had to do was win five races in a row and you're free.
这是比赛的规则
Those are the rules.
Lists 监狱里就没有规则
There are no rules in the cage, Lists.
至少对能给监狱赚钱的人来说
At least none that benefit the cage.
随便你信什么 Goldberg
Believe what you want, Goldberg.
但我觉得他们看到我们又团聚了 不是好事
But I don't think it's wise, right now, that they see us together.
欢迎来到地狱
Welcome to hell.
接着走 不要停! 快!
Keep moving, don't stop! Come on!
快点快点
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
欢迎来到Kalahari监狱 你要想越狱
Welcome to Kalahari Prison. You dare try and escape,
沙漠会比我们先出手 快走!
the desert will kill you before we do. Come on,move!
你没事吧?
You all right?
关门
Close the gate.
(比赛第一天 早晨7: 24)
嘿 Goldberg
Hey, Goldberg.
这车变大了 变强了
She's bigger and better.
大多了 也强多了
Way bigger. Way better.
我这辈子经历过的坏事
I've been through more shit in my life
比多数人十辈子经历过的还多
than most people go through in 10.
但我从来没做过的 就是欺骗或者背叛我的朋友
But what I never did was lie or betray my friends.
无论你的出发点是什么
Doesn't matter what your intentions were,
和我们分享你的秘密是安全的
your secret would have been safe with us.
我们能帮你
We could've helped.
你知道的
You know better than that.
帮我需要付出代价 我没打算让你那样
Helping me comes with a price, and I wasn't about to let you do that.
你相信诅咒吗?
You believe in curses?
这东西
This thing.
它就带着诅咒
It comes with one.
你应该信任我们的
You should've trusted us.
走吧 Lists
Let's go, Lists.
这是来自南非Kalahari监狱的现场直播
Live from Kalahari Prison in South Africa,
死亡飞车领航员之战
this Death Race Navigator Wars.
参战的有16位最美
Featuring 16 of the most beautiful,
也是最残忍的致命罪犯
ruthless and lethal convicts alive,
包括一名爱尔兰共和军恐怖分子 一名职业杀手
including an IRA terrorist, a contract killer,
和一对双胞胎连环杀手
even identical twin serial killers.
但举世瞩目的是Katrina Banks
But all eyes will be on Katrina Banks,
Frankenstein美丽的领航员
the gorgeous copilot of the notorious Frankenstein.
这是一场于死神赛跑的比赛 唯一的规则是 活下来
This is a match to the death. The only rule, survive.
这是怎么回事?
What the hell is happening?
晚上好 欢迎来到死亡飞车 赛前特别节目
Good evening and welcome to a special pre-Death Race event.
16位美丽而又致命的佳丽
Sixteen beautiful, yet deadly women,
将为十个死亡飞车领航员的名额剑拔弩张
vie for 10 spots as Death Race navigators.
她们将为能领航明天的赛事
These ladies will battle to the death to see who's worthy
而战斗到死亡
to navigate in tomorrow's Death Race.
前三分钟过后 压力感应踏板会激活一系列致命武器
After the first three minutes, pressure plates activate a variety of lethal weapons.
战斗将在还有十个人活着的时候结束
The fight ends when 10 ladies are left alive.
Katrina存活的概率非常低
Katrina's statistical probability of survival is very low.
那对瑞典的姐妹也不可能互相残杀
And the Swedish twins aren't gonna fight each other.
另外 Katrina的名声也会招来更多杀机
Plus, Katrina's celebrity will attract more attention.
这些都会给她带来变数
That changes the odds.
那 你什么意思?
So, what are you saying?
百分之七到十
Seven to 10%.
这是最好的打算
Best case scenario.
调暗灯光 大屠杀即将开始
Dim the lights. The carnage is about to begin.
Katrina 痛扁她们!
Katrina, kick some ass!
观众的数量有了吗?
Do I know my audience or what?
这是真人秀的把戏 拜托
That's reality TV shit. Come on.
好的
Yes.
压力踏板已启动
Pressure plates are now active.
推近一点 推近一点
Go in tighter. Go in tighter.
给个特写!
Get me a close-up!
杀!
Kill!
要来点爆米花吗?
Do you want some popcorn with that?
不用...
No, I don't need...
Katrina 快去拿武器!
Get to the weapons, Katrina!
快 烧死她!
Come on, cook her ass!
五号摄像机 特写! 拍Katrina Banks
Camera five, close-up! Katrina Banks.
我搞死你!
I'm gonna fuck you up!
尝尝这个!
Take this!
很好 很好!
Good work, good work!
去死吧!
You love me to death!
不!
No!
哎呀 我还真以为那双胞胎能活下来
Oh, man, I really thought both twins were gonna make it,
看看对她们的宣传啊
the way they hyped 'em up and all, you know?
别信这些狗屁
Never believe your own hype.
一定要拍下来!
Don't miss that shot!
剩下的十个人将作为明天赛事的领航员
Ten women remain who'll compete as navigatos in tomorrow's Death Race.
场上选手均为暴力犯罪罪犯 请勿在家中模仿比赛镜头
Fighters are convicted violent felons. Acts should not be duplicated at home.
放松点 Prudence 没什么可以害怕的
Relax, Prudence. There's nothing for you to fear here.
虽然他们都是无恶不作的杀人犯强奸犯
They may be ruthless, vicious murderers and rapists,
但你已经不够他们的兴奋点了
but they've taste enough to ignore you.
比赛开始啦!
It's race time, motherfuckers!
别碰我 今早的我感觉有些易碎
Don't touch me. I'm feeling a little fragile this morning.
快点 出发了
Come on, let's go.
走!
Come on!
也很高兴见到你
Good to see you, too.
去死吧
Drop dead.
- 快走!  - 好主意 不过我已经试过了
- Come on, move!  - Good idea. But I already tried that.
下一个!
Next!
下一个
Next in line.
下一个!
Next!
很好 谢谢
Nice. Thank you.
再来一个 下一个!
Another one. Next!
往我身体里打东西 你想干嘛?
What do you think you're putting inside of me?
松开他 他就是个办事儿的
Let him go. He's just doing what he's told to do.
和终端岛不一样 这里没有围墙
Unlike Terminal Island, there are no walls here.
我们可不希望看到车手开了车逃之夭夭
We didn't want our drivers dashing for their freedom.
这个会实时告诉我们你们的确切位置
This will tell us exactly where you are at all times.
那 我要是脱离了赛道 会发生什么?
So, I go off-course, what happens?
你不熟悉德制Iris-T红外智能导弹吧?
You're not familiar with the German-made Iris-T Infra-red Smart missile?
不
No.
你脱离赛道之后就熟悉了
You go off-course, and you will be.
就像Kalahari监狱不允许有逃犯一样
Just as there's no escape from Kalahari,
死亡飞车比赛也不允许有逃犯
there is no escape from Death Race.
还真不错啊
Well, ain't that somethin'?
York先生 我希望你知道 我会对你言听计从
Mr. York. While you are here, I want you to know that I am at your disposal.
任何你喜欢的东西 就是你的
Anything your heart desires, consider yours.
随便什么?
Anything?
请入座
Please do take a seat.
来自南非Kalahari监狱的现场直播
Streaming live from the Kalahari Prison in South Africa,
一个关押世上最凶残罪犯 从未被世人所知的监狱
home to the most ruthless and violent criminals the world has ever seen.
Niles York给大家带来 死亡飞车
Niles York presents Death Race.
11位车手将进行为期三天的艰苦赛事
Eleven drivers will compete over three brutal days
横穿地球上最可怕的地域之一
across one of the most dangerous terrains on Earth
就为争取一项终极大奖
for a chance at the ultimate prize.
获胜五场 重获自由
Win five races, win your freedom.
喂Lists
Lists.
这里有喇叭和麦克风 所以没有耳麦了
There's a speaker and mic here, so no more headsets.
但火控装置还在老地方
But the weapon trigger's still in the same place.
好的
Okay.
不再有防御装备
There are no shields out here.
只有用来攻击的武器
Only offensive weapons.
激活武器的位置在地图上有标示 在表格这里有提示
Weapon locations are marked on the map, indicated here on the tablet.
但记住 你要开车穿过而不是压过 来激活武器
Now, remember, you have to drive through, not over, to activate.
你觉得这会像巴哈拉力赛一样吗?
You think this thing's gonna be like a Baja race?
我对巴哈的唯一印象
The only thing I know about Baja,
就是那里的一种我喜欢的卷饼
it's a style of tacos I like.
嘿Goldberg
Goldberg,
这回我得要你帮忙
I'm gonna need you on this one.
放心吧
I got your back.
有三件事你要留心
Three things you gotta worry about.
首先是Razor
Razor.
- 选手Razor  - 比起在比赛了赢我们 他更想把我们杀了
- Razor.  - He'd rather kill us than win.
还有Nero
Nero.
- 选手Nero  - 方格子旗和赢比赛毫无关系
- Nero.  - Checkered flag has nothing to do with winning.
好的 那第三个是什么呢?
Okay. So what's the third?
第三个嘛
Third,
就是那个坐副驾驶的小妞了
it's that beautiful girl sitting next to you.
准备在线直播
Let's get it ready for an online broadcast.
大家紧密配合好 15号10号还有8号摄像机位准备
Let's make a tight MCU. Camera 15,10 and eight.
谢谢
Thanks.
未来
Gotcha.
听我说Katrina
Katrina.
别 我不想听
Don't. I don't wanna hear it.
你是我的领航小妞啊 你说英语吗?
You're my nav-girl. You, do you speak English?
当然会说 你个白痴
I speak English, you fucking idiot.
赢下这场再说
Let's just fucking win this race.
不错 这下该爽了
Wow, this is gonna be great.
选手Joker
Joker.
史上第一场这样的官方比赛
The first official race of this kind
于1967年10月31号在下加利福尼亚的Tijuana鸣枪
started in Tijuana, Baja California on October 31st, 1967...
被称作NORRA墨西哥1000拉力赛
and was called the NORRA Mexican 1000 Rally.
当年的赛道长度为849英里 也就是1366公里
The course length that year was 849 miles, or 1,366 kilometers,
终点在南下加利福尼亚的La Paz
and ended in La Paz, Baja California Sur, sir.
第一名总赛程耗时27小时38分
The overall winning time was 27 hours, 38 minutes
冠军是驾驶Meyers Manx沙漠越野车的
set by Vic Wilson and Ted Mangels
Vic Wilson和Ted Mangels
while driving a Meyers Manx buggy.
你在和谁说话?
Who're you talking to?
我以为你想听点有关的历史故事
Thought you'd appreciate some relative historical perspective.
好吧 你想错了
Well, you thought wrong.
发车灯准备
Set the lights.
10号摄像机 镜头往左
Number 10, pan to your left.
目光都聚焦在想赢得个人第五场比赛
All eyes are on Frankenstein, as he tries to win his fifth race
并第一个赢得自由的Frankenstein身上
and become the first inmate to win his freedom.
神秘的Frankenstein在赢得个人前四场飞车战胜利后
The mysterious Frankenstein became a worldwide phenomenon
成为了一个举世瞩目的传奇
after winning his first four Death Races.
但那只是在终端岛上的故事
But that was back on Terminal Island.
他能在非洲续写胜利的篇章吗?
Can he repeat that success here in Africa?
三
Three.
在这三条沙漠赛道上 选手将要继续面对
Unique challenges lay ahead as our drivers
终端岛封闭赛道上那样的挑战
move from the confines of Terminal Island's track onto three desert courses.
二
Two.
大屠杀即将开始
The carnage is about to begin.
你他妈干嘛?
What the fuck are you doing?
他抢跑了
He's jumping.
有人抢跑了
We've got a jumper.
发射导弹
Fire away.
我们被装了跟踪器怎么办?
What about our trackers?
有什么办法吗?
You know something?
你要干嘛?
What are you doing?
快跑!
Get out of here, man!
导弹来了!
It's coming, it's coming!
天呐 你在干嘛?
Oh, my God, what are you doing?
导弹来了 导弹来了
It's here, it's here, it's here.
于是The Jackal成为了死亡飞车前所未有的先例
And The Jackal becomes a Death Race first.
从未有选手在比赛开始前就已送命
Never before has a driver been killed before the race has even begun.
重置发车灯
Reset lights.
傻逼
Stupid.
真有意思
That's entertainment.
嗯 很不错 对我们有利
Well, that worked well. For us.
出发
Go.
启动啊! 赶紧的!
Start! Start!
好啊 傻逼!
Yippee ki-yay, motherfucker!
哇!
Whoa!
看看那帮傻逼!
Look at the fuckers!
这位选手是Olga Braun
Introducing Olga Braun.
- 你是要我来开吗?  - 艹 你自己看...
- Do you want me to drive?  - Fuck, it's...
死亡飞车赛事第一位女车手
Death Race's first ever female driver.
哈哈! 来吧
Yeah! Come on.
快启动 快启动啊!
Start! Start! Start!
你真是个疯子
You're a freak.
哦耶
Oh, yeah.
选手Psycho
Psycho.
嘿Goldberg 听得到吗? 在不在?
Hey, Goldberg. You getting me? You online?
准备开战了吗?
Are you ready to get serious now?
赛道很窄 所以只有弯道才能超车
The roads are narrow, so pass only on the turns.
武器直到25号路标才会被激活
Weapons are inactive until mile marker 25.
Lists 这车的最高速度是多少?
Lists, what's my top speed on this thing?
每小时100英里 但你最好开在50到60之间
100 miles per hour, but you wanna keep it somewhere between 50 and 60.
别管那些你熟悉的赛车
Forget everything you know about racing.
沙漠赛看的不是车速 而是路况和操控
Desert racing isn't about speed. It's about dirt and handling.
慢着 我还以为你对沙漠赛一无所知
Hang on a minute. I thought you didn't know shit about this kind of racing.
是啊 这是我谷歌出来的第一条
I don't. It's the first thing that came up on Google.
车手们已进入了第一个赛段
The racers enter the first leg of the race,
Katbakkies Pass沙丘
the sand dunes of Katbakkies Pass.
他就在你后面!
He's right behind you!
喂 你能不能别像一个娘们儿一样开车
Hey, stop driving like a pussy.
我长大的地方 女人都开得比你强
Where I'm coming from, the ladies, they can drive better than this.
- 往右急转  - 什么时候?
- Turn hard right.  - When?
现在!
Now!
你还想开车不?
You wanna fucking drive?
您能别说话吗?
Could you just not talk?
- 安静就好  - 滚
- Just don't talk.  - Shut up.
Luke! 你得重新找到激活武器的装置
Luke! You need to find the weapon marker again.
艹!
Fuck!
真JB屌!
That was fucking great!
- 武器激活装置在右面  - 是 我看到了
- I see weapon markers on the right.  - Yeah, I see it.
激活装置就在正前方
You see the tracking markers straight ahead.
你以为我瞎了?
You think I'm blind?
滚
Fuck off, man.
走你!
Frankenstein!
艹你妈!
Motherfucker!
Razor的武器已经激活了!
Razor's weapons are activated!
快 把大炮转过来
Come on, turn the cannon, turn the cannon around.
开快点!
Go faster!
给他们看看这比赛该怎么开
We have to show them how it's done.
你就准备挨打了?
Are you gonna take this shit?
选手14K
14K.
哈哈哈 中国佬 感觉得到了吗 中国佬?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. China. Did you get that, China?
转进来 转进来
Turn them in. Turn them in.
耶!
Yeah!
快激活大炮
Activate the cannon.
大炮已激活
Cannon activated.
Joker已经把大炮瞄准你了
Joker's got a cannon trained on you.
小心! 就在你背后!
Look out! Behind you!
把这货变成火堆吧
Let's light this puppy up.
再见啦
Bye, bye, bye.
快啊!
Come on!
干死他
Fuck him up.
你还好吗 Frankenstein先生?
Are you okay, Mr. Frankenstein?
知道吗? 我以为我不会想念我的后挡板了
You know what? I never thought I'd miss the Tombstone.
Goldberg 要你帮个忙
Goldberg. I need your help.
别试着甩掉他! 让他咬住你
Don't shake him off! Let him get right up behind you.
Goldberg 你疯了吗?
Goldberg, are you crazy?
拜托!
Come on!
- 我已经受不了这个逼样了  - 哦 真太美了
- I'm getting sick of this bastard.  - Oh, beautiful.
你这样做不符合逻辑
What you're doing is illogical.
上帝啊 感觉好棒
Oh, God, that felt good.
这样我们撑不了多久了
We can't take much more of this.
接着开Luke 相信我!
Stay on the wheel, Luke. Trust me!
你个白痴!
Fucking idiot!
现在换谁得意了 Joker?
Who's laughing now, Joker?
我必须告诉你 我非常非常满意
You know, I gotta tell you something. I am very, very impressed.
多谢 Goldberg
Nice, Goldberg.
去他娘的逻辑
Fuck logic.
有时候该怎么做得靠直觉
Sometimes you just gotta let your heart and gut tell you what's right.
两位车手已经送命 剩下的九位选手进入Khayelitsha镇赛段
Two Death Racers down. Nine remain, as we enter Khayelitsha Township.
选手Pretty Boy
Pretty Boy.
该死!
Damn!
艹
Shit.
往左 往左
Go left, left, left, left, left.
武器只在这个赛段激活
Weapons activated for this sector only.
左转!
Take left!
这里可是非洲 白痴!
This is Africa, son of a bitch!
这些人是都活腻歪了吧 别他妈站路上啊!
These people got a damn death wish. Off the fucking road!
艹!
Son of a bitch!
我们得跑了!
We need to get outta here!
别跑 和车待一起! 有追踪器的!
No, stay with the car! The tracking device!
快跑吧! 快!
Let's go! Come on! Run!
有人逃跑了
We've got a runner.
是谁?
Who?
Pretty Boy弃车逃跑了
Pretty Boy's left his car.
已经瞄准他了
We've got a lock on him.
发射
Fire.
他在一个小镇上 你就不怕误杀平民?
He's in the middle of a town. Won't you kill a lot of innocent people?
他们下辈子会咸鱼翻身的 准备好了就发射
They will be rewarded in their next life. Fire when ready.
该死!
Shit!
快闪开!
Out of my way!
艹了...
Fuck...
小心 小心
Watch out, watch out.
不!
No!
漂亮
Fucking beautiful.
- 他们来了!  - 剩下的七位车手
- They are coming here!  - Seven drivers remain,
已进入本场最后一个赛段
as they enter the last leg of stage one.
Lost区域
The Lost Zone.
该死!
Shit!
嘿Lists 知道这些人什么来头吗?
Hey, Lists, do you know anything about these guys?
他们是Kalahari的军阀
They're the warlords of Kalahari.
他们组织了这个地区74.5%的犯罪活动
They're responsible for exactly 74.5% of all organized crime in the region.
毒品 卖淫和绑架是他们三大盈利项目
Drugs, prostitution, kidnapping are their three biggest earners.
很好 就需要他们这些
Great, just what we needed.
别想了 Luke 完赛就是
Let it go, Luke. Just finish the race.
该死 这些人是参赛选手吗?
Shit. Are these people even in the game?
该死 Frankenstein
Shit. Frankenstein.
别他妈挡道啊!
Just move out of my fucking way!
这个该死的14K!
This, fucking 14K!
他冲我们来了 艹!
He's coming up behind us. Bitch!
Luke 你现在是第二名 你得超掉Razor
Luke, you're in second place. You have to pass Razor.
你在终点前的最后一个弯道了 快点Luke 加油!
You're on the last corner before the finish line. Come on, Luke, push!
- Razor赢得了第一天的比赛  - 该死!
- Razor takes day one.  - Damn!
Frankenstein已微弱差距据第二位
Frankenstein finishing a close second.
14K Olga Baby Psycho以及Nero均完成比赛
14K, Olga, Baby, Psycho and Nero have all survived.
太棒了 Satana 无可挑剔
That was amazing, Satana. Incredible job.
我觉得该庆祝一下 你说呢?
I think it's cause for a celebration, don't you?
喂Prudence
Prudence.
滚蛋 顺便叫剩下的人都可以滚了
Fuck off and tell the rest of them to fuck off, too.
大家都出去
Everybody out.
我说 大家都出去!
I said, everybody out!
接着走! 快点 都出去!
Keep moving! Come on, get out, everybody!
嘿 今天你干得不错
Hey, you did well today.
看见没 是不是想上我了? 你现在就想上我了
You see, you wanna fuck me now don't you? You wanna fuck me now.
天呐 她现在就想上我了 女人啊
God, she wants to fuck me now. Typical.
你真想现在就上我吗?
Do you really wanna fuck me now?
Katrina 听着 我知道我搞砸了 好吧?
Katrina. Look, I know I fucked up, okay?
我就是想保护你
I was just trying to protect you.
你知道太多不安全
It wasn't safe for you to know.
我们回不到过去了
We can't be what we were.
第二名 你在放水啊
Second place. You're slipping.
Lists 开始把这车修好吧
Lists, let's get this thing cleaned up.
喂Frankenstein!
Frankenstein!
想都别想!
Oh, no fucking way!
- 怎么回事!  - 隧道里有人打架 是Frankenstein
- What the hell is going on!  - A fight in the tunnel. It's Frankenstein.
快把他弄出来 快!
Get him out of there. Now!
出去 现在!
Now, get out!
医生呢! 快来一个医生!
Doctor! We need a doctor!
医生呢!
Doctor!
George Villiers 第一位白金汉公爵 Crazy Horse乐队
George Villiers, 1st Duke of Buckingham, Crazy Horse,
亨利三世 亨利四世
Henry III of France, Henry IV of France.
我会有事吗?
Am I gonna be all right?
你没事的
You're gonna be fine.
就是皮肉伤
It's just a scratch.
我现在要你把裤子脱了
Now I'm gonna need you to drop your trousers.
有这个必要吗?
Is that necessary?
怎么了? 我没事吧?
What? Am I all right?
你好得很
You're going to be fine.
是不是该悄悄透露一下 我可是你们的铁杆粉丝哦
What I probably should have disclosed, I'm a big fan of yours.
有多铁?
How big?
歌手和作曲人Elliott Smith 当然 还有凯撒大帝
Singer/songwriter Elliott Smith and, of course, Julius Caesar.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
嗯 我在列举最著名的被刺人物
Well, I'm listing the most notable stabbing victims.
他没事的
He's gonna be okay.
我得见见他
I gotta see him.
他怎么样?
How is he?
好得很哦
Wonderful.
姑娘们 我觉得我们应该给我们的大明星Frankenstein
As girls, I thought it would only be fitting to offer Frankenstein,
一点奖励
our new celebrity, an incentive, a prize,
一场免费的做爱
a free fuck.
好啊 宝贝儿!
All right, honey!
Amber 起来 走吧
Amber, get up, move it.
快点
Hurry up.
享受一下吧 小妞!
Get it, girl!
该和你的男朋友说再见咯
Say bye to your boyfriend, honey.
MLGB的!
Fucking bitch!
有人在上你的男人哦!
Someone's fucking your boyfriend!
奖励
A gift.
Frankenstein吗?
Frankenstein?
是我
Yeah.
那么
So,
我觉得我们可以谈谈合同的条款了
I was hoping that we could discuss the terms of our contract.
我计划每年六场比赛 至少三年
I was thinking six races per year, three year guarantee.
- 是吗?  - 是的
- Oh, yeah?  - Yeah.
你考虑得怎么样了呢?
And how much did you have in mind?
我让Martine做了个标价
I got Martine to put together a bid.
哦 是吗?
Oh, you did, did you?
你逗我玩儿吧?
You gotta be kidding, right?
这样吧 我们先看看明天比赛怎么结束
Do you know what? Let's just see how this one concludes tomorrow
再谈以后的比赛
before we discuss any future races.
但我必须说 我对迄今为止的赛事
But I gotta tell you, I am very, very pleased
非常非常满意
with how things are going so far.
我没想到比赛会这么轻松
I didn't think it would be this easy.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我以为那个疯子会弄出点事儿 他们都说他很禽兽
I was expecting issues with the freak. They told me he was a monster.
他就一娘炮儿啊
He's a pussycat.
你别小看他
Do not underestimate him.
我和那个人做了个交易 我指望他讨价还价来着 但他没有
I made a deal with the guy. I was expecting him to renegotiate. But he didn't.
他在打自己的算盘
He's planning something.
嗯
Hmm.
(比赛第二天 早晨6: 58)
别拿你的眼睛强奸我 该出发了
Stop fucking me with your eyes and let's get on with this.
这他妈是干嘛?
What the fuck is going on here?
你他妈第一次看一个白妞裸着吗?
The first time you see a white nincompoop naked?
快走! 妈的! 快走
Come on, move! Damn it! Come on. Shit.
- 怎么样?  - 嘿
- What's up, baby?  - Hey.
开始吧
Let's do it.
Lucas人呢?
Where's Lucas?
你在这里干嘛?
What are you doing here?
该说实话了
Truth time.
听着 我有我的道理
Look, I had my reasons.
但我没和大家说实话 我很抱歉
But I haven't been straight with you. And I'm sorry for that.
但我决定改正错误
But I wanna make this right.
好啊 那就别再骗我们了
Well, then don't lie to us again.
好的 听着 比赛里的一些事情得让你们知道
Okay. Look, there's something you all need to know about the race.
我的确和新的老板做了交易
I did make a deal with the new boss.
要故意输掉比赛
To lose.
输掉比赛? 想开这车输掉不容易啊
To lose? You'll have a tough time losing in this car.
我知道 但是他可拿枪顶着我脑袋
I know. He had a gun to my head.
他还威胁要你们的命
He had a gun to all of your heads.
所以我又做了个交易
So, I made a new deal.
我们这么办
And this is what we're gonna do.
欢迎来到死亡飞车第二阶段的比赛 还有七位车手
Welcome to stage two of Death Race. Seven drivers remain.
放松地躺好 大屠杀即将开始
Sit back, relax. The carnage is about to begin.
登录后能看到您最喜爱的车手的内部资料
Log on and get inside access on your favorite drivers.
只需加一小笔额外的钱 您就能看到
For an additional cost, you can tap in
来自赛车内闭路摄像机的画面
to the closed circuit camea inside the driver's car.
死亡飞车
Death Race.
真是一个风和日丽
It's a beautiful day
适合送死的好天
to die.
Nero暂时领先 后面跟着Frankenstein
Nero is in the lead, followed by Frankenstein,
14K Razor还有Olga
14K, Razor and Olga.
神奇的Psycho位居第六 Baby在第七位
The surprising Psycho is sixth. And Baby is seventh.
武器系统已经就位了?
So, weapons are active now, yes?
是 以及不是 有点小把戏
Yes and no. There's a little twist.
喔!
Ooh!
车手们正走上Keiskie路 直插Dry Lake
The racers approach Keiskie Road, heading towards the Dry Lake.
听着 他们在搞鬼
Look, they're throwing you a curve ball.
25英里之内只有这一个激活武器的地方
That weapons marker you see is the last one for 25 miles.
第一个开过的人才有武器 但你要是死了 那个装置会重新启动
First one thru it gets the weapons. But if you die, the weapon marker reactivates.
所以剩下的人都会盯上你
So, everyone's gonna be on your ass.
因为我做或者不做 都是个死 对吧?
It's because I'm damned if I do, damned if I don't, right?
说对了小子 完全正确
You got it, homes. Exactly.
激活装置就在那儿
Here's the weapon marker.
激活装置就在你左面
Weapon marker's coming up on your left.
好的 就在那儿
Okay, over there.
Luke快啊!
Luke!
快到了快到了 快! 加油啊! 好的!
Almost, almost, come on! Come on, make it! Yes!
Olga抢到了武器激活
Olga wins the weapons marker.
去他妈的
Fuck it.
嘿 抱歉啦 姑娘们
Hey, sorry, ladies.
她们才不是姑娘
Those aren't ladies.
别小心眼儿
Don't get jealous.
看着点儿路
Get your eyes back on the road.
没问题
Sure.
Olga就在前面
There's Olga, up ahead.
艹!
Fuck!
MLGB的
Son of a bitch.
哦耶
Oh, yeah.
看来不该这样来
Maybe this wasn't such a good idea after all.
为什么?
Why?
因为他们现在都冲着我们来了啊
'Cause they're all after us now.
去你妈的!
Fuck this!
喂 快把那逼撵出去啊!
Man, you get the bitch out of the way. Come on!
我真太坏了
I'm a bad man.
哦耶!
Oh, yeah!
该死!
Oh, shit!
耶!
Yeah!
- 把这逼撞出去  - 见鬼去吧
- Knock this bitch out the way.  - Kiss your fucking ass.
喔!
Whoo!
我说的吧
I told you.
小妞你想怎么样?
What you gonna do, bitch?
你有什么打算?
What you got?
来啊 来啊
Come on. Come on.
- 尝尝这个!  - 哦 该死!
- Eat this!  - Oh, shit!
激活装置就在前面
Weapon marker's dead ahead.
好的
Okay.
双杀之后赛道上还剩五辆赛车
The double kill leaves only five cars in the race,
他们正进入Calvinia镇
as they head into Calvinia Township.
天呐 肯定有人惹毛他们了 看着很不友好
Jesus, somebody pissed them off. I don't think they're friends.
看来我们不是很受欢迎啊
They really don't like us.
是啊 我已经习惯了
Yeah, I'm getting used to that.
能把火焰喷射器准备起来了吗?
Why don't you warm up that flame thrower?
终于开始了!
Finally!
当心!
Watch out!
来啊!
Come on!
你不能开快点吗?
Fucking roll, will you?
喔!
Whoa!
我勒个去 简直屌爆了啊!
Holy shit, that's awesome!
好啊 喜欢这样是吗?
Okay. It's like that, huh?
该死!
Damn it!
能开火了
Fucking fire.
棒极了
All right.
该死的!
Son of a bitch!
好的!
Yeah!
Luke! 小心 Razor追近了
Luke! Watch, Razor's coming closer.
他去我们后面了
He's coming up behind us.
想玩是不是? 了结吧
Do you wanna play? Let's end this.
- 艹!  - 该死的
- Bitch!  - You fucker.
我受不了这人了
Man. I'm sick of this asshole.
别以为我看不到你了!
I can see you, devil!
你说什么?
What?
你们要干嘛? 别碰我
What the fuck are you doing? Get off me.
真是太美了
This is just so fucking beautiful.
这 给Nero的赛程画上了句号
And that marks the end of Nero.
在这最后赛段 我们还剩下四位选手
As we enter the final stage, we're down to the final four.
回程穿过Loeriesfontein到达终点
Driving back through Loeriesfontein to the finish line.
我们看看今天军阀们都有什么家伙
Let's see what the warlords of Kalahari have in store today.
武器激活装置已准备激活
Weapon markers ready for activation.
好的 有武器了
Okay, we're clear.
现在就激活
Get me weapons now.
抓好了
Hang on.
往哪里跑呢? 我们还没完呢
Where's he going? We're not done yet.
你想干嘛?
What the fuck you want?
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
嗯?
Huh?
谁在干什么?
What's who doing?
你死定了!
You will die!
这是为了什么?
What was that for?
为了救你的命
To save your ass.
走走走
Go, go, go.
有人跟上来了
We got company.
该死!
Shit!
二号摄像机 拍下来
Camera two, pick that up.
混蛋!
Motherfucker!
这些人是谁啊?
Who the fuck are these people?
没事 我能搞定
It's okay. I got it.
朝你来了
Coming up behind you.
去死吧 混蛋!
Die, you bastard!
这真是棒极了
This is just fucking awesome.
是啊
Yeah.
你跑不了的 混蛋!
You can't run, motherfucker!
这个会很给力的
This is gonna be close.
现在你怎么办?
What now, Luke?
开始了
It's on.
二号摄像机 推近
Camera two, pan in.
二号机 跟上啊!
Camera two, move it!
这些镜头别丢了 快点
Let's not lose that shot, boys. Come on.
动作快 想把这镜头丢了?
Move it, move it. Do you wanna miss the fucking shot?
太赞了
Awesome.
第二天的赛程以一场爆炸结束
Day two concludes with a bang.
欢迎明天继续回来 收看史诗般的大结局
Tune in tomorrow for the epic conclusion.
任何转播以及未经授权的使用者将被处以死刑
Any rebroadcast or unauthorized use is punishable by death,
小于15岁的将被处以终身监禁
or life in prison if under the age of 15.
我都不知道他有孩子
I didn't know he had a child.
难以置信 居然对最亲近的人知之甚少
Shocking how little we know about the ones closest to us.
我也一点不了解我的秘书
I know virtually nothing about my secretary here.
相反 她知道我生活的每一面
Conversely, she knows every aspect of my life,
私人的 工作的 好的坏的 还有丑陋的
personal, business, good, bad and ugly.
转过来看着我
Turn around and face me.
对于Goldberg的事情我很抱歉
I'm sorry to hear about Goldberg.
我都没听说过他 但我知道他对你团队的重要性
I never knew the man, but I know how integral he was to your team.
你这种人怎么可能会知道?
What possible understanding can a man like you know about that?
他岂止是团队的一份子 他是我的亲人
He was more than just a part of my team. He was family.
嗯
Hmm.
不绕弯子 我们说好的还作数 对吧?
Just to be clear, our deal still stands. Yes?
你现在不要被感情冲昏了头脑
Now, don't let your emotions cloud your judgment.
明天14K会赢
14K will win tomorrow.
你会落后完赛 官方说法是因为机械故障
You're gonna stall out. Officially, mechanical failure resulted in your loss.
我可不想大家觉得那是你的最高水准
I don't want it to look like you were beat.
不能坏了你的名声啊 是吧?
Can't damage your rep now, can we?
明白了吗?
Are we clear?
我问你问题 你就要回答 明白了吗?
When I ask you a question, you answer me. Do you understand?
不 不全明白
No. Not really.
现在你脑子里别惦记什么赢比赛
Now get these foolish thoughts of winning out of your head.
你明天会输 不然天助我也
You will lose tomorrow, or so help me God,
我把你关进我能找到的最黑最阴暗的牢房
I will put you in the deepest, darkest cell I can find.
你被关在里面 为那个死了的机械师哭鼻子的时候
And while you're down there, crying about that dead spic,
好好想想我会怎么处理你的小妞
just imagine what I'll be doing to your girlfriend.
- 你想多了  - 你想怎么样?
- Bad idea.  - What are you gonna do?
- 威胁杀了我?  - 其实不然
- Threaten to kill me?  - No.
你错了 Niles
No, Niles.
这样你就解脱得太轻松了
That would be letting you off too easy.
你能活过明天 但是你不能赢比赛
You can live tomorrow, but you can't win.
大概吧 目测你得把眼睛睁睁大吧? 和所有人一样
Maybe. Guess you'll just have to tune in, huh? Like everybody else.
不不不 我得跟你悄悄地说
No, no, no, no. I need to talk in private.
我能听到
I hear you.
想跟我说什么吗?
Is there something you wanna say to me?
我就是在想
I was just wondering
你是不是原来的那个Frankenstein
if you are the original Frankenstein.
为什么呢?
And why is that?
你想想啊
Think about it.
面具背后到底是谁呢?
Who is the man behind the mask?
嗯? 有人知道吗?
Hmm? Does anybody know?
他们就是要一个禽兽
They just want the monster.
他们可以像杀别人一样把你弄死
And they can take you out in a way that would kill a normal human being,
转身就把你的衣服给另一个人套上
and then just slap the suit on the next guy and hey, presto.
Frankenstein又活了
Frankenstein lives.
你觉得他们会杀了我?
You think they're gonna kill me?
不 Frankenstein永远不会死
No. Frankenstein can never die.
他可以被枪杀 出车祸葬身火海 被炸身亡
He can be shot. He can crash and burn. He can explode.
但Frankenstein总能复出
But Frankenstein will always emerge.
也许受尽摧残 但总是活着
Battered and bruised, maybe. But alive.
只是不断续写他的神话
Just makes his legend even greater.
是的 是的 他和我说话了
Yes. Yes, he spoke to me.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
这是什么意思?
What is the meaning of this?
这 是我的事情
This is my business.
这是我出的节目
This is my production.
不 这是我的节目 我的!
No, this is my production. Mine!
你的团队都急着把它还有你卖掉
And your network was more than eager to sell it and you out.
看来你用不着投标了
Guess you won't be needing that bid now.
刚才那下我就不计较了
I'll give you a free pass for that one.
但要是你还想来
But if you try anything like it again,
我会保证你被吊起来 再亲手把你送进这个监狱
and I will have you chained up and I personally will pimp you out
最恶心的疯子的牢房
to the nastiest fucking psychos in this prison.
喂 你 停下
Hey, you, stop.
守卫
Guard.
让她过来
Let her through.
你们几个 让我们单独待会儿
All of you. Leave us.
我觉得我们应该给我们的大明星Frankenstein
I thought it would only be fitting to offer Frankenstein,
一点奖励
our new celebrity, an incentive, a prize,
一场免费的做爱
a free fuck.
你和她...
So did you...
上床了?
sleep with her?
没有
No.
你知道我为什么没有 是吧?
And you know why I didn't. Right?
喂 你 继续拖地!
Hey, you. Get back to work!
去吧
Go.
(比赛第三天 早晨8: 36)
我不会让你失望的
I won't let you down.
虽然我没有统计数据为我这句话作证
Though I don't have any statistical evidence to back up that statement,
但我有强烈的预感...
I feel strongly...
Lists 除了你 没有人能帮我了
Lists, there's no one, no one I'd rather have watching my back.
谢谢你 Luke
Thanks, Luke.
介意给我坐吗?
Do you mind?
来吧
Let's do this.
好的各位 听着
Okay, people, listen up.
无论发生什么 Frankenstein今天都不能赢
Whatever happens today, Frankenstein cannot win.
所以把你们的眼睛都睁大了
So, keep your eyes open.
欢迎收看死亡飞车的最后赛程
Welcome to the final stage Death Race.
所有人都看着一个人
All eyes are on one man.
Frankenstein 他已成为死亡飞车历史上最有竞争力的选手
Frankenstein. He's been the most dominant driver in Death Race history.
但他能再坚持一天 赢得自己的自由吗?
But can he hold on for one more day and win to earn his freedom?
烧死他们
Torch these bitches.
让你的心指引你
Let your heart and gut guide you.
你能行的 你能行的
You can do this. You can do this.
Luke 小心三号弯道 是个大半径的转弯
Luke, watch out for turn three. It's a massive turn.
我讨厌这音乐
I don't like this music.
能换个别的吗? 上帝啊 我真恨死这歌了
Can you get something else? God, I hate this music.
嗯 这个好 这个好
Yeah, that's nice. Yes.
Frankenstein继续保持着微弱的优势
Frankenstein continues to hold a slim lead,
车手们正朝Red Rock路进发
as the drivers reach Red Rock Road.
离开了先前的区域 武器必须被重新激活
Leaving sector. Weapons must be reactivated.
激活装置就在前面
Weapons marker coming up.
乖 别出岔子
Come on, play nice, motherfucker.
抓好了 Katrina 我已经受够这个人了
Hang on, Katrina. I've had enough of this guy.
抓稳了
Hold on.
怎么样? 摸着很舒服哦
Yeah? It's nice.
拜拜啦 亲
Adios amigo.
- 有意思  - 快走!
- Cool.  - Get out!
你个混蛋 Razor! 我还活着 不会放过你的!
You bastard, Razor! I'm still alive and coming for you!
不!
No!
水! 救命! 救救我! 给我水
Water! Help! Help me! Water.
Psycho死后 剩下Frankenstein
The Psycho's death leaves only Frankenstein,
14K和Razor继续厮杀
14K and Razor left alive to compete.
选手们进入采石场 向终点进发
The racers enter the quarry, heading to the finish line.
Frankenstein刚获得了武器 目前领先 要赢了
Frankenstein just got weapons, and he's in the lead, about to win.
他还不够格
He's gonna need more than that.
准备好导弹
Ready the missiles.
你要当着全世界观众的面把他杀了
You wanna kill Frankenstein while the whole world watches,
观众不会放过你的
the audience will never forgive you.
你会害死这比赛的
You will kill the fucking show.
杀他 是我的事!
It is mine to fucking kill!
目标已锁定
Target's locked.
他离终点太近了
He's too close to the finish line.
你会害死很多人的
You could kill dozens of people.
知道吗Prudence? 你说对了 每次都说对
You know what, Prudence? You're right. You're always right.
你被炒了
You're fired.
怎么站在这里? 快滚啊!
You're still here? Get out of my sight now!
好的
Okay.
发射
Fire.
二位 该准备一下了
Hey, guys. Get ready for some company.
该死
Shit.
那个跟踪器
It's the tracking device.
哦 该死
Oh, fuck.
- 什么?  - 激活反制装置!
- What?  - Activate countermeasures!
这回躲不过了
We're not gonna make it through this.
该死
Oh, shit.
激活了
Activated.
发射!
Fire!
开玩笑
No way.
不可能!
No fucking way!
你说你有几条命?
How many lives do you have?
嗯 我猜至少还有一条
Well, at least one more, I guess.
他怎么活下来的?
How the fuck did he survive that?
你说跟踪器是万无一失的
You told me that tracking device was foolproof.
谁设计跟踪器的?
Who designed it?
你的公司
Your company did.
嘿Lists 帮我接通14K的车
Hey, Lists. Patch me through to 14K's rig.
帮我接14K
Patch me through to 14K.
- 接上了  - 能通话了?
- You're up.  - You got him?
Luke 你可以和14K通话了
You're on with 14K, Luke.
嘿 14K
Hey, 14K.
- 多谢了  - 不客气
- Thank you.  - You're welcome.
我们现在扯平了
We're even now,
Lucas先生
Lucas.
- 准备好了吗?  - 结束这一切吧
- Are you ready?  - Let's finish this.
我来杀你了
I'm coming to kill you.
听到没 Niles?
You hear me, Niles?
我来杀你了
I'm coming to kill you.
亲自过来把你做了 听到了吗 Niles?
Personally coming to kill you. You hear me, Niles?
把广播都打开 都打开!
Open all mics. Open all mics!
守卫们 请注意
Attention, guards.
Frankenstein正朝终点过来 杀了他!
Frankenstein is headed to the finish line. Take him out!
懦夫
You're such a coward.
出去 出去!
Out, out!
你说对了 他把我耍了
You were right. He screwed me over.
我之前该听你的 你想让我怎么做?
I should have listened to you before. What do you want me to do?
快啊!
Come on!
打死他!
Take him out!
快 射击!
Come on, shoot him!
快啊!
Come on!
该死!
Fuck!
你去哪儿?
Where do you think you're going?
你以为我会让一个劳改犯 毁了我造就的一切吗?
You think I'm gonna let a simple fucking con ruin everything that I've built?
Frankenstein直逼终点
Frankenstein has a clear path to the finish.
他就要赢了
He's about to win.
14K 超过了Frankenstein 冲过了终点
14K pulls past Frankenstein and crosses the finish line.
好的!
Fuck yeah!
14K赢得了本场比赛
14K wins the Death Race.
该你赢的
You could've won that.
我知道 但输赢已经不重要了
I know. It's not about winning races anymore.
他输了 哈哈 都结束了
He lost. It's over.
不玩儿了
No more games.
别高兴太早
I wouldn't say that.
准备好了?
You ready?
准备好了
Yeah, I'm ready.
我爱你
I love you.
丫头 外面见
See you on the other side, kid.
我要亲手杀了他
I'm gonna take him out myself.
等一下
Wait.
你哪儿也别去
You aren't going anywhere.
- 我... 把钥匙给我!  - 和你的节目一起去死吧
- WTF... Give me the key!  - This is your production. It's quite fitting that you go down with it.
把这东西弄开!
Get this fucking thing off me!
我非常遗憾地宣布 Niles York已经死亡
It is my sad duty to announce the death of Niles York.
这位充满理想的企业家带给了我们死亡飞车
The visionary entrepreneur who brought Death Race to us,
却在比赛的最后一天遇害
died in an explosion that also claimed the life of Katrina Banks
爆炸也夺走了Katrina Banks的生命
on this third and final day of competition.
我们向York先生的家人和朋友表达最诚挚的哀悼
We'd like to extend our deepest sympathies to Mr. York's family and friends.
还有人活着!
Someone's alive!
他真是Frankenstein吗?
Is this really Frankenstein?
是的 他是Frankenstein
Yes. Yes, it is Frankenstein.
追踪装置确认了他的身份
The tracking device confirms it.
是的 我可以确认Frankenstein在爆炸中幸存
Yes, yes. I can confirm that Frankenstein has survived
并正在返回终端岛的途中
and is currently en route back to Terminal Island.
我把重建死亡飞车比赛的任务交给各位
I leave the task of rebuilding Death Race in your very capable hands.
死亡飞车的家 就是终端岛
Death Race's home is Terminal Island.
不再会是别的地方
Nowhere else.
我已经为Frankenstein重新选择了团队
I've arranged a new pit crew leader for Frankenstein.
他们的信息都在你们面前的资料里了
You should have his information in front of you.
是的是的 这些都没问题
Yes, yes, that's all well and good.
但Frankenstein怎么办?
But what of Frankenstein?
我获悉Frankenstein已脱离昏迷
I've been informed that Frankenstein is alert,
意识清醒 将在两周后出战
conscious, and will be ready to race in two weeks.
抱歉
Excuse me for a minute.
怎么了?
What happened?
他醒过来一直在叫 说胡话
He just woke up screaming, rambling a bunch of nonsense.
我不是Frankenstein!
I'm not Frankenstein!
他明显还受着大量的刺激
He's obviously still in shock.
我们找他的朋友来安抚他
We brought his friend down to calm him down.
Frank吗?
Frank?
我他妈再说一次
For the last fucking time,
我不是Frankenstein
I am not Frankenstein.
你确定吗?
So you're absolutely sure?
是他 但我从没见过他这个样子
It's him all right. But I've never seen him like that before.
Prudence 告诉他们 告诉他们我是谁 我是Niles York
Prudence, tell them. Tell them who I am. I'm Niles York.
我不是Frankenstein!
I am not Frankenstein!
不!
No!
宝贝儿 你好啊
Hello, baby.
还好吧?
Is everything okay?
不
No.
是好极了
It's perfect.
行了 小鸳鸯们
All right, lovebirds.
你从来都这么可靠
We can always rely on you.
- 为Lists干杯  - 为Lists干杯
- To Lists.  - To Lists.
收到我的汇款了吗?
Did you get my wire?
嗯 我在看呢 真是太...
Yeah, I'm looking at it right now. It's very...
真是太大方了 谢谢你
Very generous. Thank you.
冲着你把那混蛋害这么惨 我都会付三倍的钱
For what you did to that bastard, I would have paid triple.
之前可没说啊
Well, if I'd known that.
我还以为是计划要把他弄死呢
I thought the plan was to kill him.
计划赶不上变化 对吧?
Well, things change, huh?
个人认为 这比杀了他更到位
Personally, I think I did better than that.
- 你有异议吗?  - 哪里哪里
- Are you complaining?  - Hell, no.
你是怎么做到的?
How the hell did you pull it off?
那混蛋把你害惨了 是不是?
That son of a bitch screwed you over, didn't he?
我帮你做这个 只有一个条件
We do this, one condition.
我和他做了个交易
I made a deal with the guy.
你输了你活下去 你赢了你见鬼去
You lose, you live. You win, you die.
有些事情得告诉大家 我的确做了笔交易
There's something you all need to know. I did make a deal.
和我们前一任老板
With our old boss.
Weyland吗?
Weyland?
我还指望他来讨价还价 但他没有
And I expected him to at least renegotiate. But he didn't.
千万别小瞧他
Do not underestimate him.
他有自己的计划
He's planning something.
按我的做法 用我的规矩和我的计划
My way, my rules, my plan.
我要你帮个大忙
I'm gonna need something very important from you.
是什么?
And what's that?
我得杀了你 Goldberg
I'm gonna need to kill you, Goldberg.
他们是Kalahari的军阀
They're the warlords of Kalahari.
听着 我要让这些军阀卷入比赛
Look, I'm gonna bring these warlords into the race.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
谁在干什么?
What's who doing?
趁大家都在看比赛的时候 我要你自杀
While everybody's watching, I'm gonna need you to take yourself out.
我要一个信号
I'm gonna need a signal.
要很响
It's gonna be loud.
你要我做什么?
What do you need me to do?
我们要找个内应
We need someone on the inside.
好
Done.
安全了
The coast is clear.
对那个机械师的死我很抱歉
I'm sorry to hear about that dead spic.
这是我的节目
This is my production.
你是对的
You were right.
出去 出去!
Out, out!
他把我耍了
He screwed me over.
我之前该听你的
I should have listened to you before.
Frankenstein朝终点来了 杀了他!
Frankenstein is headed to the finish line. Take him out!
为了你自己 现在听我的
Do yourself a favor and listen to me right now.
我要亲手杀了他
I'm gonna take him out myself.
你要我怎么做?
What do you want me to do?
把他困在房间里 不择手段
Keep him in the room. No matter what.
钥匙给我!
The fucking key!
死亡飞车有它的终极大奖
Death Race has the ultimate prize.
你能赢得你的自由
You win your freedom.
一切由Frankenstein开始 一切由他结束
This all starts and ends with Frankenstein.
还有人活着!
Someone's alive!
我就是在想
I was just wondering
如果你是原来那个Frankenstein
if you are the original Frankenstein.
是 他是Frankenstein
Yes, it is Frankenstein.
追踪装饰证实是他
The tracking deve confirms it.
Frankenstein永远不会死
Frankenstein can never die.
他可以被枪杀 出车祸葬身火海 被炸身亡
He can be shot. He can crash and burn. He can explode.
但Frankenstein总能复出
But Frankenstein will always emerge.
Frankenstein 他就是死亡飞车
Frankenstein, he is Death Race.
Carl Lucas 愿他安息
Carl Lucas, may he rest in peace.
嘿! 安全了
Psst! The coast is clear.
我不走了
I'm not going.
什么叫你不走了? 你必须跟我们走
What are you talking about you're not going? You have to.
我从来适应不了外面的日子
I was never any good out there.
弄不懂那些世故
I didn't understand the rules.
只有监狱里 才有我弄得懂的规矩
In prison, things make sense.
而且 总得有人垫后
And, plus, someone has to stay behind.
要一个目击证人来说故事
A witness to tell the tale.
你这么做不符合逻辑
What you're doing isn't logical.
他说的没错
Yeah, he's right.
有人曾和我说过
Someone once told me,
去他妈的逻辑
fuck logic.
让你的心告诉你该怎么做
Let your heart tell you what's right.
我和Weyland谈过 我来帮你们
I spoke to Weyland. I'm here to help you.
平面图 电子系统 还有通风井的位置
Blueprints, electrical systems, ventilation shafts.
如此一来 没有他 你这拷贝不走样的节目
Now, how would your little copycat event play
怎么继续下去?
without the game's marquee star?
那是个戴着面具的人
It's a man in a mask.
观众怎么会知道哪个才是真的?
How would the fans know which one was real?
这就是你会失败的原因
That's why you're going to fail.
年轻的亿万富翁会变成一个笑话
The boy wonder billionaire will become the laughing stock.
你们所知和所爱的死亡飞车不会被改变
The Death Race that you all know and love will not change.
它会变得更壮大更完美 这 我向大家保证
It will grow bigger and better. This, I promise.
你现在要是突然改变比赛规则
Now, if you suddenly change the rules of the game,
你就留不住观众了
you're going to lose your audience.
你怎么打算 找人替我? 找谁呢?
What are you gonna do, replace me? With who?
这结局你不会喜欢的
Payback's a bitch, son.
我是Frankenstein
I am Frankenstein.
我会复仇的
And I will have my revenge.